dream11.com 2013-04-25

# Fantasy Cricket Portal | Privacy Policy | Dream11.com

Dream11.com is the flagship brand of Clover Media Private Limited (“Dream11.com”). Dream11.com is a cricket portal which also operates cricket-based fantasy games and other online games. 

Any person utilizing Dream11.com (“User”) or any of its features including participation in the various contests, games (including fantasy games("Game")) **(“Amusement Facilities”)** being conducted on Dream11.com shall be bound by this Privacy Policy. 

Dream11.com respects the privacy of its Users and is committed to protect it in all respects. With a view to offer an enriching and holistic internet experience to its Users Dream11.com offers a vast repository of Amusement Facilities. Kindly take time to read the 'About Us' section to know more about Dream11.com. Most of the Amusement Facilities are offered for free but you may need registration to participate in Dream11.com's online games. The information about the User is collected by Dream11.com as (i) information supplied by Users and (ii) information automatically tracked during User's navigation on Dream11.com. 

**Registration:**

To avail certain Amusement Facilities on our websites and on our Facebook application, Users would be required to provide certain information for the registration process namely:

1\. Dream11.com ID   
2\. Password   
3\. Email address   
4\. Date of birth 

User Invitations:

In the course of providing the Amusement Facilities, Users may invite other existing Users or other users (“Invited Users”) to participate in any of the Amusement Facilities by providing the email address or Facebook username of such users. Dream11.com may thereafter use this information to contact the Invited User and invite such user to register with Dream11.com (if such Invited User is not a existing User) and participate in the Game/Amusement Facility in relation to which such person was invited by the User. The participation of the Invited User in any of the Amusement Facilities shall be subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions for the use of the Dream11.com website (available here). The User hereby represents that the Invited Users have consented and agreed to such disclosure to and use of their email address and Facebook username by Dream11. 

All required information is specific and based on the kind of Game/ Amusement Faciity the User wishes to participate in or access,and will be utilised for the purpose of providing services, including the Amusement Facility, requested by the User. The information as supplied by the Users enables us to improve our Amusement facilities and provide you the most user-friendly game experience.We may also share such information with affiliates and third parties in limited circumstances, including for the purpose of providing services requested by the User, complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services. 

Where we propose to use your personal information (that is, information that that may be used to identify the User and that is not otherwise publicly available, such as the User’s or Invites User's name, email address, address and date of birth) for any other uses we will ensure that we notify you first. You will also be given the opportunity to withhold or withdraw your consent for your use other than as listed above. 

To improve the effectiveness & usability of our game sites for our Users, we use "cookies", or such similar electronic tools to collect information to assign each visitor a unique random number as a User Identification (User ID) to understand the User's individual interests using the identified computer. Unless the User voluntarily identifies himself/herself (e.g, through registration), Dream11.com has no way of knowing who the User is, even if we assign a cookie to the User's computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information supplied by the User. A cookie cannot read data off the User's hard drive. Our advertisers may also assign their own cookies to the User's browser (if the User clicks on their ad banners), a process that Dream11.com does not control. 

Dream11.com's web servers automatically collect limited information about User's computer's connection to the Internet, including User's IP address, when the User visits our site. (User's IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send data to the User -- such as the web pages viewed by the User). The User's IP address does not identify the User personally. Dream11.com uses this information to deliver its web pages to Users upon request, to tailor its site to the interests of its users, to measure traffic within its site and let advertisers know the geographic locations from where Dream11.com's visitors come. 

Dream11.com also includes links to other websites. Such websites are governed by their respective privacy policies, which are beyond Dream11.com's control. Once the User leaves Dream11.com's servers (the User can tell where he/she is by checking the URL in the location bar on the User's browser), use of any information provided by the User is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site which the User is visiting. That policy may differ from Dream11.com's own. If the User can't find the privacy policy of any of these sites via a link from the site's homepage, the User may contact the site directly for more information. 

When Dream11.com presents information to it's online advertisers -- to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our website -- it is usually in the form of aggregated statistics on traffic to various pages within our site. When you register with Dream11.com, we contact you from time to time about updating your content to provide features which we believe may benefit you. 

All information gathered on Dream11.com is securely stored within Dream11.com-controlled database. The database is stored on servers secured behind a firewall; access to such servers being password-protected and strictly limited based on need-to-know basis. However, we understand that as effective as our security measures are, no security system is impenetrable. Thus, we cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. Further, any information you include in a posting to the discussion areas will be available to anyone with Internet access. 

Dream11.com also believes that the internet is an ever-evolving medium. We may periodically review from time to time and change our privacy policy to incorporate such future changes as may be considered appropriate. Our use of any information we gather will always be consistent with the policy under which the information was collected, regardless of what the new policy may be. 

We use third-party advertisers to serve ads when you visit our websites. These advertisers may use information (excluding your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services which might interest you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here: Several deceptive emails, websites, blogs etc. claiming to be from or associated with Dream11.com may or are circulating on the Internet. These emails, websites, blogs etc. often include our logo, photos, links, content or other information from any of Dream11.com. Some emails, websites, blogs etc. call the user to provide login name, password etc. or that the user has won a prize/ gift or provide a method to commit illegal/ unauthorised act or deed or request detailed personal information or a payment of some kind. The sources and contents of these emails, websites, blogs etc. and accompanying materials are in no way associated with the Dream11.com. For your own protection, we strongly recommend not responding to emails or using websites, blogs etc. 

Any questions or clarifications with respect to this Policy can be sent to Dream11.com at: [legal@Dream11.com](mailto:legal@Dream11.com) or by normal/physical mail addressed to:

Clover Media Private Limited   
Unit No 7, Basement   
B Wing, Trade World   
Kamala City, Senapati Bapat Marg,   
Lower Parel (West)   
Mumbai, INDIA
